sup everyone David with all these people
a few has a very special video today
yeah I was hesitant on you making this
video in the first place but I feel like
I needed to to protect Sonic on the
ground
glowy alcohol some of you may have
already seen that be it up going around
on YouTube Bailey call though I don't
even remember the time of the video it
was like um everything wrong with soccer
in a minute or some [ __ ] up
I don't even remember the guy who made
this video because mainly because they
were long tickets stupid [ __ ] why would
I have met Lenny Harris I mean for
mention there's no anyways so I thought
you know what [ __ ] this [ __ ] in the end
I'm gonna make encounter a free meal to
let the true the people who truly will
you find out about smart guys all make
the beer to show them there's nothing
wrong with talk on the ground and a view
if you listen closely you on low anyways
Oh first off I'll say this if you what
you want to feel I highly recommend down
go look at yourself because I am NOT up
I'm not about to link it up put a
[ __ ] a link to that [ __ ] in my
description because dear God get that
get that GD pile of [ __ ] away from my
channel inches okay now all explaining
why this vid that video is stupid as
[ __ ] they boost up the explain bad that
home
I know what better but it's so stupid
oh yeah he said like you don't even have
to watch the series Oh even after long
what kind of [ __ ] is bad he said he
says the whole show can be explained
I'm just watching to open it what am I
the only with this [ __ ] I don't look
like that
it just don't I mean you can watch you
can watch GOP nobody may say the time
finds I'm a [ __ ] mama Queen lien of
us yeah you may tell you that but that's
the point of the show you're so funny
watching soccer Manic and Sonia look for
the [ __ ] mafia with them on their
adventure I mean that's the whole point
of this [ __ ] you know they try to find
their mama but you have to you have to
go through the pain and [ __ ] a box there
then like almost fun like only finding
who in some [ __ ] mother but then she
gets away and not only that but they
don't you explain that um but the going
to be done just plain like they don't
have a dad I mean what the [ __ ]
what [ __ ] buy the DVDs everybody knows
they view bother
do they have [ __ ] home damn a [ __ ]
robe you talking about what happened to
the dad he's [ __ ] dead Ben I mean he
also he goes arms you talking like how
the opening makes a mistake bike home
son Mac and Sonya the leader of the free
of fathers when the now early I've gotta
admit that's kind of true but clearly
politically they done that because I the
openings was made when they were very
old enough to do you can we knock before
that
I mean not only thank you he doesn't
even talk about any of the later
absolute still raw white detail he has
not even watched that show like he has
not even watch talk on the ground I mean
come on [ __ ] if you good back at
Shirley's watch the [ __ ] I mean down
know what [ __ ] what I mean why you gotta
be a [ __ ] poopy baby [ __ ] I mean you
only take it down with it
come on I don't do that I don't do that
[ __ ] I mean [ __ ]
Hey he supposedly said it in nine
minutes or less but if you want to do it
you know it's not I mean Lucas he is he
is always having to line up to you but
you know talking like three things in
the hallway he's like keep rewinding
[ __ ] because it's an odd make it very
obvious now what have to epsilon 1 which
let's face it that's [ __ ] meet you was
Bobby the prisoner if you want then you
know how good that is because we have
all these tips but anyways yep this
video this video I'm just letting you
all know you're not going to watch that
[ __ ] it's [ __ ] if you would you
watch something good stay on my channel
it's gonna watch it I'm the only true
friend left up some speed animate some
awesome bar Donna's videos and Mindy
video perlite and yeah